操
Fuck!
好的  这里有十个数字四个空
Okay, I've got ten numbers, four spots.
我需要一个四位的密码
I need a four-digit code.
不  别别别
No, no, no.
狗日的  又怎么了
Shit! What now?
操
Shit.
老天爷啊
Jesus Christ.
线索
Clues.
操  好的好的
Shit. Okay.
没什么卵用
That's nothing.
跟随光明  去往绿茵
"Follow the light to greener pastures."
什么意思  这他妈又是什么意思
What does that mean? What does that mean?
光  什么光
Light? What light?
光  跟随光
Light. Follow the light.
绿色  绿色的书  对
Green. Green book, yeah.
绿茵  好吧  就是这个
Greener pastures. Okay. Yeah, all right.
历史洪流中  众生死去
"At any point in history, to watch another die,
时间之谜明了  唯汝善终
unveils time's great mystery, while leaving you alive."
时间  时间  跟什么钟有关
Time. Time. Some kind of clock.
操
Shit.
哪来的钟
Where's the clock?
他妈的没看见有钟啊
I don't see a goddamn clock!
众生死去  噢我知道了  没错
"To watch another person die." Yeah. Okay, yeah.
操
Oh, shit!
好了  他们指着什么  让我找找
Okay. They're pointing! Let's see.
和时间有关  是时钟上的指针  对吧
It's time. It's hands on a clock. Yeah.
这个是四点  四点钟
That one's four! Four o'clock!
八
Eight.
六
Six!
二  就是这些数字了  这就是密码
Two! That's the number, that's the code!
好了  四在哪呢  操  快点啊
Okay. Where's the four? Shit. Come on.
好了好了  对了没错了
All right. Okay. Yeah, good.
快啊快啊  八
Come on, come on! Eight!
六
Six.
老天啊
Oh, my God.
在哪呢  六  六
Where's the... Six, six, six!
天啊
Oh, God!
二  二  好了  快开啊
Two, two! Yeah. Okay. Come on.
快啊
Come on.
开啊  为什么没开啊
Come on! Why isn't it working?
操他妈的
Oh, shit.
开啊
Come on.
开  给我开门啊  开门啊
Open! Come on, open!
操 没路能出去
Oh, God, there's no way out!
放我出去吧
Please get me out!
操  不要
Shit! No!
不要啊
No!
《密室逃生》
(芝加哥  伊利诺伊州)
有人听说过
Has anyone ever heard the saying,
越盯着壶  水越不开吗
"A watched pot never boils"?
其实  从量子学上讲兴许也不无道理
Well, on a quantum scale, that may actually be true.
有人知道什么叫做量子芝诺效应吗
Does anyone know what the quantum Zeno effect is?
哇  没人知道吗
Wow, guys, not all at once now.
其实  这可能是量子物理学上
Well, it may well be
最古怪的现象之一了
one of the oddest things in quantum physics.
简单来说就是  观察使运动停止
Simply put, observation stops movement.
在你观察微粒的时候他们不会发生改变
Atoms won't change while you watch them.
好了  就到这里了
All right, that's all the time we have.
祝你们假日愉快  节后再见
Have a good holiday. See you after the break.
感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving.
佐伊  我能和你谈谈吗
Zoey, can I talk to you for a minute?
我读了你关于芝诺效应的论文
I read your paper on the quantum Zeno effect.
你想要被关注
So, you want to be heard.
你想要分享知识
You want to share what you know,
但又不想离开宿舍  走出舒适圈吗
but only in the safety of your own dorm room?
我会努力多跟人沟通的
I'll try and speak up more.
你可能觉得应该减少你人生的变量
It might seem like reducing the number of variables
去控制最后得出的结果
in your life will control the outcome,
但人生可不是什么科学实验
but life isn't a science experiment.
你不能永远保持在自己的世界里
You can't contain your world forever.
放假的时候去试试
Try doing one thing
做一件自己不太敢做的事情  好吗
that scares you over break, okay?
好的
Okay.
(J.W的车位)
雷  我是杰森  听着
Ray, it's Jason. Listen.
你想在退休之前买一条船  对吗
You want to buy a boat by retirement, right?
那就持续关注着低贝塔系数的股票
Well, keep focusing on these low-beta stocks,
很快你就有一艘有桨的划艇了
and it's going to be a rowboat with rented oars.
截止到第一季度
By the end of the first quarter,
股市将会回升百分之十
the market's going to see a 10-percent return,
到时你已经在船上赚到百分之三十了
while you'll be sailing away with 30.
嘿  你不会后悔的
Hey, you won't regret it.
你肯定觉得我是炒股界的宫城先生吧  查理
I must be like the Mr. Miyagi of trading to you, Charlie.
宫啥先生
"Mr..."
天爷啊  小子  你哪年生的啊
Jesus Christ, kid, what year were you born?
他是个很睿智的日本老头
He's this wise, old Japanese man
他教一个小孩空手道  然后去打败其他小孩
who taught a kid karate so he could beat up other kids.
阿克曼先生在一号线上等你
Mr. Ackerman for you on line one.
赌一百块有人要送我礼物了
100 bucks says I'm getting a gift.
恭喜你啊  阿克曼先生  你在庆祝吗
Congratulations, Mr. Ackerman. Are you celebrating?
噢  谢谢  谢谢你  阿克曼先生
Well, thank you. Thank you, Mr. Ackerman.
不不不  我可不能收礼
No. No, no, no, I couldn't accept a gift.
私人飞机  去大溪地吗
A private jet. To Tahiti?
哇
Wow.
你家在那
Your home there. Uh-huh.
这个听起来是个很棒的假期啊
Now, that sounds like a hell of a weekend.
如果可以用筷子夹住苍蝇
Man who catch fly with chopstick...
就没什么别的能难住你了
accomplish anything.
你肯定是新手光环吧
You, beginner luck.
上蜡  脱蜡
Wax on, wax off.
嘿  盖瑞  我  呃
Hey, Gary. I, uh...
我听说
I heard there was...
前台收银有个岗空出来了
an opening up front at checkout.
我很想加薪
I could use the bump.
我正在努力搬出我妈家
I'm trying to move out of my mom's.
最近她风格有点抽筋
It's starting to cramp her style.
听着  我体谅你  小子
Look, I feel for you, kid.
我真的很理解  你知道的
I really do. You know, I do.
只不过你去前台会有损我们的生意
It's just putting you out front would be bad for business.
好吧
Yeah.
反正我也不是干顾客服务的料
Yeah, I'm not cut out for customer service shit anyhow, so...
本
Ben
你得找个更健康的排解方式
you've got to find healthier ways to unwind.
出去溜溜  交交朋友
Go outside, make a friend.
-我不是有意  -没事  抱歉
- I didn't mean to... - It's fine, it's fine. Sorry.
好的  谢了  盖瑞
Yeah. Thanks, Gary.
快递员给你送来了这个
A messenger dropped this off for you.
是阿克曼先生送的
It's from Mr. Ackerman.
可不是吗
Of course it is.
最好是辆特斯拉的钥匙
This better be keys to a Tesla.
打破陈规  思维无限
"For always thinking outside the box."
看起来阿克曼先生已经
Well, it seems like Mr. Ackerman has graduated
把兴趣从单一麦芽威士忌转到打不开的盒子上了
from sending single malts to boxes that don't open.
是啊  富人都怪怪的
Yeah. Rich people are weird.
钱虽买不来幸福
Money can't buy you happiness.
但最好自己的痛苦自己花钱解决 查理
You better afford your own brand of misery, Charlie.
-感恩节快乐  -随你吧  我明天还会来的
- Happy Thanksgiving. - Whatever. I'll be in tomorrow.
∮ 听说睡着和死亡是兄弟 ∮
∮ They say sleep Is the cousin of death ∮
嘿  现在还来得及
Hey, offer still stands.
你真的不想
Are you sure you don't want to come
来我家过感恩节吗
to my family's for Thanksgiving?
谢谢你  但是  你知道的
Thank you, but, you know,
我受不了那种一大家子人围着吃饭的气氛
big family dinners aren't really my thing.
行吧
Okay.
你知道吗  能有点属于自己的时间我还挺激动的
You know, I'm really psyched about having time to myself.
我早就想尝试那个
I've been wanting to take a stab
立方体猜想了
at one of those cuboid conjectures for, like, forever.
真的超酷的
It's really cool, actually.
它表示三个单一变量多项式的不可约性
They claim irreducibility of three univariate polynomials
如果这个猜想是真的的话
with integer coefficients and if that is true,
那么欧拉的完美立方体理论就不成立了
then Euler's concept of a perfect box can't exist.
超棒
Wow.
你知道吗  有时候我怀疑是不是你知道我不会去问度娘
You know, sometimes I wonder if you just make up words
你就编出这些东西来唬弄我
because you know I won't Google them.
别再来了
Not again.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
没事  抱歉
Yeah, I'm sorry.
我要走了
Well, I'm out of here.
好的
Okay.
嘿  这是给你的
Hey, this is for you.
你的教授给的
It's from your professor.
-好的  -等下
- Oh. - Wait.
你们俩不会有一腿吧
You guys aren't doing it, are you?
什么  没有
What? No.
那么  你就好好玩你的
Well, have fun playing with your...
盒子吧
box.
再见  艾莉森
Bye, Allison.
拜拜
Bye.
开启新世界
"Open new doors."
逃离的机会
"A chance to escape."
要记得  解谜盒很靠直觉
Remember, the puzzle box is intuitive.
不能强迫
You don't want to force it.
噼啪  噼啪  然后
Snap, crackle, and...
我  恨  你
I hate you.
我初二数学都没及格  竟然给我解这个
Give this to the guy that failed eighth grade math.
想的真美啊  盖瑞
Great idea, Gary.
这真是太浪费时
This is the biggest waste of...
以此米诺斯密室逃脱入场凭证
"This serves as an entry voucher for Minos Escape Rooms."
首位逃离沉浸式房间的玩家
"Be the first to escape our most immersive rooms yet
可以获得一万美元
and win $10,000."
请尽快于官网回复
"RSVP at minosescaperooms.Com."
嗨
Hi.
这就是那个什么米诺斯楼吗
This is the Minos building?
-应该是吧  -谢了
- I think so. - Thanks.
是啊  吸烟有害健康  我知道
Yeah, it's going to kill me, I know.
你好
Hi.
我是来玩密室逃脱的
Yeah. I'm here for the escape room.
请出示身份证
ID please.
谢谢
Thanks.
能这么做的男人一般都要先请我吃晚饭
Most guys buy me dinner first.
请您上交手机
I need to collect your phone.
真的吗  为什么
Really? Why?
我们这不允许解谜的时候拍照发微博
You can't be Twittering pictures of the puzzles.
-好吧  -三楼
- Okay. - Third floor.
好的  谢谢
Okay, thanks.
谢谢你的服役
Thank you for your service.
等一下  等一下
Hold the door, please.
我总是会再偷带一个手机进来
I always sneak in a second one.
等候室实在太无聊了
The waiting rooms can get so boring.
太棒了
Yes!
请先就坐  很快会有人陪同
Please have a seat. Someone will be with you shortly.
好的  谢谢
Okay, thanks.
非常有礼貌啊  是吧
Quite the welcome wagon, isn't she?
超友好的
Super friendly. Heh.
-嘿我是迈克尔  叫我迈克  -我是阿曼达
- Hey, Michael. Mike. - Amanda.
-你叫阿曼达吗  -是啊
- Your name's Amanda? - Yeah.
-太有趣了吧  -怎么了
- Isn't that funny? - What?
我家养了只狗就叫阿曼达
I had a family dog growing up named Amanda.
她超可爱  是哈士奇和科利牧羊犬的混血
She was a cute, little husky-collie.
两只眼睛还不是一个颜色
Two different colored eyes, actually.
很独特的  真的
It was very unique. Yeah.
挺酷的
Cool.
是啊  她很酷  不过后来她死了
Yeah, she was cool. Yeah, and then she died.
你也知道  狗活不久
You know, dogs die.
搭便车时出了事故
Hitchhiking accident.
那你还能玩游戏吗
Can you still play video games?
不  不行了  真可惜
No. No, man. Unfortunately I can't,
我只能和成年女性做爱来打发时间
so I just have sex with adult women to fill the time.
-好吧  -没错
- Okay. - Yeah.
不好意思  你好啊
Sorry. Hi.
-你好  -我们是不是认识
- Hi. - Do I know you?
不  应该不认识吧
No, I don't think so.
是吗  我看你很眼熟
Really? You look really familiar to me.
你是不是上过电视啊
You're not on TV or something, are you?
好吧  这下可有得受了  你们好
Well, this is going to suck. Hi.
你好
Hey.
要签到吗
Sign-in sheet?
噢别担心  她挺忙的
Yeah, don't bother. She's preoccupied.
你好啊  我是迈克
How are you doing? Mike.
-我是本  -本啊
- Ben. - Ben.
我猜你也收到了个盒子是吧
I'm guessing you got a box too, huh?
是的
Yeah.
你花了很久打开吗
Did it take you long to open it?
不算很久
It didn't take me too long.
是啊  我们都收到了盒子
Yeah, we all got boxes.
打开它还不算难
Opening it was the easy part.
你们看了官网吗
So, the website for this place made the games
看起来挺有趣的  对吧
look pretty fun, huh?
是啊  看起来很像真实的电子游戏
Yeah. They're basically like real-life video games.
-是吗  -那么说
- Really? - So, you've done
你以前玩过这种的吗
one of these before.
我玩过93个房间了  都是大房间
I've done 93 rooms. Yeah, all the big ones.
避难屋啊  谜团室啊  地下室啊什么的
Panic Room, Enigma, Basement...
越狱啊  突入啊  密室啊  当然还有解锁的
Breakout, Break In, Lock In. Lock Down, of course.
还有地堡  有一战主题  二战主题
And bunkers World War One, World War Two...
冷战啊  波尔布特的复仇啊
Cold War, Pol Pot's Revenge.
那你们呢
What about you guys?
你肯定很擅长这些  对吧
You must be really good at these, huh?
是啊  挺会玩的
Yeah. I'm pretty good.
这可不酷
It's not cool.
是啊  你知道吗我的侄子和你一模一样
Yeah. You know, my nephew's like you.
他很迷这些
He's completely obsessed. He burns through
他把零用钱都花在在密室逃脱上了
all of his allowance money on escape rooms.
我就是因为他才来的  他帮我报的名
He's the reason why I'm here. He signed me up.
好像这个密室在一些聊天室里
And apparently this room was rated
被评为最顶级的密室逃脱
one of the top in the country on some chat room.
没错
Yeah.
我的怪胎富豪客户把这个当礼物送我了
My weirdo rich client gave this to me as a gift.
有点强制的意思
It felt mandatory.
是啊  花钱让人把自己锁在一个房间里
Yeah, paying people to lock me in a room
看起来对我不怎么有吸引力啊
never seemed too appealing to me.
怎么了  什么改变了你的想法
Yeah? What changed your mind?
-哈  哈  一万美元啊  -我也这么想
- Ha, ha. Uh...$10,000.  - Yeah, me too.
要我说  这可算是一大笔钱了
That is a big chunk of change in my book, you know?
从之前受伤以后
Yeah. I've been driving an 18-wheeler
我就一直在开大货车
since I had this injury a while back,
我最近读到有种可以自动驾驶的汽车
and I've been reading about these self-driving cars.
听说卡车运输行业
And I heard that the trucking industry's
将会第一批试水自动驾驶技术
going to be the first one to get automated,
在那些机器人取代我之前
so I'm trying to just squirrel away a few nuts
我要努力多攒点钱
before the robots come to get me.
-这可真扫兴啊  兄弟  -这就是我的生活
- That was a real buzzkill, man.  - It's just my life.
这种事真的难以置信  居然会给现金做奖金
This one's got to be really insane for there to be a cash prize.
网上说目前还没有人成功逃出来过
The website said no one's been able to escape it yet.
如果我们做到了  我们可是要出名了
If we're able to do that, we're going to have
你们根本想象不到
so much street cred. You have no idea.
有什么规则或者限制吗  之类的
Are there rules and regulations? What?
你只需要在时间结束前逃出去
You just have to escape before the clock runs out.
如果没逃出去呢  会怎么样
Well, what happens if you don't?
工作人员会进来
Some guy comes in through the door
向你解释你没注意到的线索
and explains all the clues you missed.
让你看起来像一个蠢蛋
He makes you feel like a total idiot.
游戏什么时候开始
When does the game start?
我们要等游戏大师来
We are waiting for the Games Master
他会给我们讲一下背景故事
to come in to give us the story
然后带我们去密室
and take us to the escape room.
比如说  僵尸大灾变要来了
Like, it's a zombie apocalypse and we have to find
我们要在被生吞活剥之前找到解药
the cure before we get eaten alive.
我喜欢这个  听起来挺有意思的
I like that one. That one sounds good.
趁这个游戏大师还在找车位
While the Games Master is looking for a parking spot,
我要去抽根烟
I'm going to go smoke a cigarette.
操  呃
Shit. Um...
门把手掉下来了
Hey, the doorknob came off.
-什么  你弄坏了它吗  -当然了
- What, you broke it?  - Of course he did.
我没弄坏它  是它自己坏掉的
I didn't break it, it broke.
你也是这么粗鲁的打开自家房子的门吗
Is that how you open a door in your house?
这样不对  别这么粗鲁
No. Well, don't be so rough with it.
好吧  打扰一下  小姐  女士
Well, excuse me, miss. Ma'am.
天啊  这棒极了
Oh, my God, this is awesome.
你们听我说  我觉得这就是那个密室
You guys, you guys, I think this is the escape room.
什么
What?
等等  你说什么
Wait, what?
好吧  这想是烤箱的刻度盘  也就是说
Okay, it looks like an oven dial, which means
这应该是一个密码锁
it's probably a combination lock.
好了  所有人  搜一下这个房间
All right, everyone search the room.
等等  现在就开始了吗
Wait, wait. It's starting right now?
是的
Yes. Oh!
那我们要找什么东西呢
What are we looking for here, bud?
任何看起来像是拼图或者密码的东西
Anything that looks like a puzzle or a code.
数字很重要  可能在任何地方  任何东西上
Numbers are very important. It could be anything, anywhere.
或许在这下面
Maybe under here.
你要我继续拿着把手吗  还是说
Do you want me to hold on to this or is it...
对  拿着门把手吧  兄弟
Yeah, just hold your knob there, guy.
挺好的  很有意思
Great. Very funny. Yeah.
(我们知道你有一个选择)
(烤肉月刊《焦痕》  余无坦医生)
嘿  大伙
Hey, guys.
这些东西都是寄给同一个人的
these are all addressed
叫余无坦医生
to the same guy, this Dr. Wootan Yu.
这应该是一条线索吧
I mean, that's got to be a clue, right?
也许这就是背景故事
Maybe that's the story.
也许他是个邪恶的科学家
Maybe he's like an evil scientist
在他把我们缝合成
and we have to escape his lab
什么医学大怪兽之前
before he sews us all together
我们要从他的实验室中逃走
into some sort of medical abomination.
你是说  他的邪恶实验室有等候室
So, his evil lab has a waiting room?
-是吧  -不可能是
- Yeah.  - No.
操蛋的  糟了
Shit. Shit, shit.
大家伙  快看  我找到了一个星形螺丝刀
Guys, look, look. I found a star-head screwdriver.
这一定有点用吧  是吗
That's got to be something, right?
太好了  那  我们要寻找螺丝吗
Great. So, we're looking for screws?
差不多吧  这又不是锤子
Well, this isn't a hammer.
-那是星形的螺丝刀吗  -是吧  应该是
- That's a star-head, right?  - I think so. Yeah.
书名叫《华氏451》
That's Fahrenheit 451.
好吧  看起来她找到了点线索
All right, she's got something.
-什么声音  -我不知道
- What was that?  - I don't know.
那有用吗
Did that do anything?
好吧
Okay.
-好吧  那还挺酷的  -没错
- All right, now that's pretty cool.  - Yeah.
有人带防晒霜了吗
Anybody got suntan lotion?
你刚才做了什么
What did you just do?
我只是觉得那本书给出了烤箱刻度盘的密码
I just thought the book was the code for the oven dial.
能关了它吗
Turn it off, please.
这东西可真会制热啊
Wow, it's really throwing off some heat.
是啊  有点暖和
Yeah, it's warm.
确实挺热的
It's kicking some heat.
那是什么  巨大的烤箱制热线圈吗
What are those, giant oven coils?
-快关了它  -对不起  它卡住了
- Turn it off.  - I'm sorry. It's stuck.
我弄不动它
I can't move it.
操  这可太热了
Shit. This is crazy hot.
-能关了它吗  -糟了  这样吧
- Can you shut it off?  - Shit. Okay.
别再碰如何东西了  好吗
Don't touch anything else, okay?
嘿  那个  游戏男  来一下
Hey, you, gamer boy, there.
我们应该做什么  我们怎么才能逃出去
What do we do? How do we get out of here?
当卡关的时候  你可以请求一个提示
When you're stuck, you can ask for a hint.
提示  还能这么做吗  好吧  那就来吧
A hint? That's an option? Okay, great. Here we go.
对的  但是如果我们自己解谜的话会更有意思的
Yeah, but it's way more fun if we do it ourselves.
说的对  游戏男
Good one, gamer boy.
我有点想靠自己解谜
I kind of want to do it ourselves.
你好  打扰一下
Hi, excuse me.
-我们想要个提示  可以吗  -有人在吗
- We'd like our hint now, please.  - Yeah, hello.
请入座  很快就会有人来找你们的
Please have a seat. Someone will be with you shortly.
不是的  打扰一下  我们真的想问个提示  求你了
No, yeah, excuse me, we'd really like our hint, please.
请入座  很快就会有人来找你们的
Please have a seat. Someone will be with you shortly.
-她之前也是这么说的  -所以呢
- She said that last time.  - So?
她用同样方式说的  同样的断句  同样的语气
She said it the exact same way. Same cadence, same tone.
他们找的配音演员应该不是朱迪·丹奇吧
Well, the actors they hire aren't exactly Dame Judi Dench.
有人吗  我喜欢朱迪·丹奇
Hello? Hello? I love Judi Dench.
我不觉得那个水晶球会有用  兄弟
Yeah, I don't think the snow globe's going to help, man.
朋友们  这里有一个锁
Hey, guys, there's a lock over here.
对的  锁在密室逃脱中是非常重要的成分
Yes. Locks are a super important part of escape rooms.
好吧
All right.
看起来我们需要一把小小的钥匙
Okay, it looks like we need a small key
才能去到隔板的另一边
to get to the other side of the partition.
那里可能有下一条线索
That's probably where the next clue is.
好吧  我可就没什么用了
Well, I'm not going to be any help there
因为我总是找不到自己的钥匙
because I can never find my keys.
真好笑啊  或者我们不能直接打破隔板吗
Hilarious. Or we could just break it off.
这正好里就有一个灭火器
There's an extinguisher right here.
好主意
Yeah, good idea.
不不不  我们不应该借助外力
No, no. We shouldn't have to use force.
这条规则我忘记告诉你了  我的错
That's actually the one rule I forgot to tell you. My bad.
又弄坏了  好吧
Good one. Great.
你可真擅长弄坏东西啊
You're really good at breaking stuff, huh?
这个是塑料做的
It's plastic.
什么声音
What was that?
和上次是同样的声音  是吗
That's that same sound, right?
兄弟  你刚刚做了什么
Man, what the hell did you just do?
我操
Oh, shit.
我操  看起来跟真的一样
Oh, shit, that looks real.
他们只是想吓吓我们而已
They're just trying to give us a scare
算是一种沉浸式体验了
as part of the immersive experience.
你怎么什么都知道  他们付你钱了吗
What the hell, are they paying you?
并没有  我只是知道怎么玩的开心  大概吧
No, I just know how to have fun, I guess.
热中风就是你所谓的玩开心吗
Heat stroke is your idea of fun?
越来越热了
It's getting warm.
没那么糟的  把外套脱了吧
Hey, it's not that bad. Just take off your jacket.
没有人觉得这一切都有问题吗
Hey, does anyone else have a problem with this?
嘿  大家  我觉得我找到了钥匙
Hey, guys, I think I've got the key.
等等  等一下  听我说
Whoa, hey, there. Listen, short stuff...
在你让这地方更热前
let's talk about this
让我们好好谈谈
before you bring tiki torches out of the walls, okay?
等一下  她拿到了钥匙
Hold on now. She's got a key.
为什么不直接把钥匙插进去呢
Why don't we stick it in the keyhole?
好吧  我的错  那就试试吧
Okay, yeah. My bad. Let's try it.
试一下吧  来吧
Give it a shot, come on.
请入座  很快就会有人来找你们的
Please have a seat. Someone will be with you shortly.
这是真他妈诡异
Well, that's creepy as hell.
好吧  我来  让开
Fine. Yeah. I'll get it. Move.
喂
Hello.
欢迎来到米诺斯
Welcome to Minos,
世界上最杰出的密室逃脱设计师
the world's preeminent designer of escape rooms.
为了使您获得最佳的游戏体验
To get the most out of your game,
我们建议您遵守所有的规则
we recommend following all posted rules.
嘿  嘿  喂  有人吗
Hey. Hey. Hello? Hello?
那边是谁接的电话  他们说什么了吗
Who was it? What did they say?
是电话录音
It was a recording.
最后说了要遵守所有的规则
It said to follow all the posted rules.
什么规则啊
What posted rules?
糟了
Oh, shit.
不是吧  是我动了什么吗
No. Did I do that?
不不不  这他妈是什么狗屁地方
No, no. What the literal hell?
停下来吧  我受够了
Please stop. Okay, I'm done.
我是真的受不了了
I am gonna stressing out in this place
别这样  你这样会给每个人施加压力的
No, no. You're stressing everyone out here, okay?
去喝点水  把外套脱掉吧
Just go get some water and take off your damn jacket.
我们会找到方法逃出这烤炉的
We've got to find a way out of this Easy-Bake Oven.
冷静  看着我  看着我  阿曼达
Okay, look at me, look at me. Amanda.
他妈的
Oh, shit.
那是风扇吗  他们是在吹热气吗
Are those fans? Are they blowing hot air?
我们去喝点水  好吗
We'll just get some water, okay?
过来跟我一起喝点水吧
Come and get some water with me.
我没事
I'm fine. Okay.
这里越来越热了
Yeah, it's getting hot,
我们不会出事的
but nothing is going to happen to us.
-烤炉里还有风扇  -是的  那又怎样
Ovens have fans. True, but so what?
我们应该找到规则是什么吧
We've got to find the posted rules.
我不在乎那些规则
I don't care about the posted rules.
窗户那边可能会凉快点
It might be colder by the windows.
我要烤焦了
I'm burning up.
快点  我们怎么才能逃出这里
Come on, how do we get out of here?
坐着不动是不会帮你解决问题的
You're not going to solve anything by sitting on your ass.
我没有干坐着  我在动手呢
I'm not sitting on my ass. I'm on my hands and knees.
你们三个在做什么呢  找点线索啊  快点
Hey, what are you three doing? Look for something, come on.
这里太热了  你还指望我能做什么
It's too hot. What do you want me to do?
女士们  过来吧  水喝够了吧
Ladies, come on, enough with the water.
快过来帮我们一起找找
Get over here and help us look.
我们需要弄清楚线索意味着什么
We just have to figure out what the clue meant.
等等  这是什么
Hold on. What's this?
这不可能是游戏的一部分吧
There's no way this is part of the game.
线索都在什么地方啊
Where are all the clues at, huh?
大家能不能快点  这里越来越热了
Guys, come on. It's getting hot in here.
我们应该找些东西砸开这扇门
We've got to find something to break this door open.
兄弟  我们不能借助外力
Dude, we're not supposed to use force.
得了吧
Come on!
这还得熬多久  我们怎么才能出去
When is this over? How do we get out?
越来越热了  我们要生生被烤熟了
It's getting hotter. We're being baked alive.
大伙儿  放松
Guys, relax.
这真有病  是谁做的这些
This is sick. Who does this?
别这样  本
Come on, Ben.
你还想让我做什么  我什么都找不到
What do you want me to do? I can't see anything.
大家伙  我们要集中精神专心找线索
Guys, we need to focus and find the clues.
这里有150度了吧
It's like 150 degrees in here.
嘿  佐伊  那些画
Hey. Hey, Zoey, the painting.
我的天  那里有个出口
Oh, my God. There's an exit.
真的要热成狗  终于找到出口了
Oh, hot dog, look at that.
佐伊  再来一遍  你刚刚做了什么  再做一次
Zoey, do that again. Whatever you did, just do it again.
这是个通风管道  应该是个出路
Hey, guys, it's a duct. It could be a way out.
大家看  这边还有好多茶杯垫
Guys, there are more coasters here.
按住茶杯垫
Get on the coasters.
大家同时按下茶杯垫
Everyone try pressing down at the same time.
天啊  甚至桌子都是热的了
God, even the table's hot.
就这样吗  我们赢了游戏吗  太好了
Is that it? Did we win the game? Yeah.
我先走  太好了  我们赢了
I'll go first. All right, we win the game.
等等  你不会想是把我们留下来
Whoa, whoa. Wait, you're not going to just leave us
让我们一直按着茶杯垫吧
with our dicks in our hands.
有人想让他先走而不是我吗
Does anybody prefer this guy go instead of me?
-我就知道会这样  -真的吗
- That's what I thought.  - Really?
管道通往哪里
Where does it go?
-有多深  -挺深的
- How deep does it go?  - It goes pretty far.
天啊
Jesus Christ.
手要烤成猪蹄了
It's broiling.
这里真的热极了
It's not getting any cooler in here.
天啊  我迫不及待想到下一个密室了
Oh, my God. I'm so excited for the next room.
-还有一个密室吗  -杰森
- The next room?  - Jason?
嘿  我应该找到出路了  但被个护栏挡住了
Hey, I think I found a way out! It's blocked by a grate.
-迈克  把螺丝刀带过来  -好的  那东西就在我口袋里
- Mike, bring that screwdriver.  - Yeah! It's in my pocket.
来人帮我拿出来  过来  阿曼达
Someone get it out of my pocket for me. Come here, Amanda.
有人想替他按着茶杯垫吗
Does anybody want to take the screwdriver?
-我来吧  交给我吧  -你确定吗
- I've got it, I've got it. Go.  - Are you sure?
没问题的  快去吧
Yeah. Go, go.
去吧  你能做到的  迈克
Just do it. You've got this, Mike.
快点吧  这里真的热极了  动作快点
Go, man. It's not getting any colder. Hurry up, go.
-迈克  你在哪  -我来了
- Mike, where you at?  - I'm coming.
这就像是互动式餐厅剧院
Hey, hey. Just think of it like interactive dinner theater.
天啊  你说这话可没用
Jesus Christ, you're not helping me here, man.
好吧  我让这更糟了  我的错
Okay, yeah. I'm making it worse. My bad.
你磨磨唧唧干什么呢
Are you going to come today or what?
-你在下面小心点  -你在上面小心点
- Watch your face down there.  - You watch your face up there.
快点  快点  快啊
Come on. Come on, come on.
嘿  弄好了  你们快来吧
Hey, I got it. You guys, come on!
你想先走吗  阿曼达  你应该先走
Do you want to go? Amanda, you should go.
好的  那你来按着这些
Okay. Okay, here, take these.
好  他来按着这个  我按着那个
Okay. He can take that. I'll hold it.
好了  去吧  你能做到的
Okay. All right, come on. You've got this.
好了
All right.
我觉得结局是不可避免的
I feel like we're avoiding the inevitable conclusion here.
手会不够用的
We're running out of hands.
我有个主意  过来  把你的脚放在这里
I've got an idea. Come here. Put your foot on here, please.
好
Ow. Ow. Ow. Okay.
这是最糟糕的扭扭乐游戏了
This is the worst game of Twister ever.
动作能快一点吗
Can we move a little faster, please?
这不管用  操
It didn't work. Shit.
好吧  可能得盛满水
Okay, maybe it needs to be full.
-我觉得我要晕过去了  -好了
- I think I'm going to pass out. - Okay.
加油  快点  快快快
Come on, come on, come on. Come on!
-你可以把脚拿开了  -好
- You can move your foot. - Okay.
-起作用了  -太好了 太好了
- It worked! - Yes, yes.
阿曼达
Amanda？
要不你去帮她一把
Hey, why don't you just go help her?
我们来装玻璃杯的水
We'll fill the glasses.
别装作有骑士风范  老兄
Stop being chivalrous, dude.
这儿没人想跟你上床
No one here wants to have sex with you.
-快去  -好的
- Go! - Okay.
好  真不错啊  本
Nice. Really nice, Ben.
见鬼
Shit.
-快点啊  -好
- Come on. - Okay.
她进去了  快去  快点快点
She's clear. Go, go, go. Come on.
快点啊  狗娘养的
Come on, you son of a bitch, please.
快  快  快啊
Come on, come on, come on.
阿曼达  阿曼达  我就在这儿
Amanda? Amanda, I'm here.
好了  很好
Okay. Good.
怎么了  你可以呼吸的  你没被卡住
What's wrong? You can breathe. You're not stuck.
跟着我吸气  一  二
Breathe in with me. One, two...
还要两杯
Two more.
那不是现实  你没被困住
This is not real. You're not stuck.
你没事的  我在这儿  好吗  我握着你的手
You're okay. I'm here, okay? I'm holding your hand.
我保证会一直在这儿  你没事的
I promise I'm right here. You're okay.
好的  再来一杯  一杯就好
Okay, we need one more. We just need one more.
妈的  我们没水了
Shit, we're out of water.
现在我们该怎么办
What are we supposed to do now?
我怎么知道  你才是专家
How would I know? You're the expert here.
我们快到了  就快了  我保证
We're really close. We're really close, I promise.
这都是你的错
This is all your fault, you know.
-什么  -就因为你
- What? - You're the reason
阿曼达喝光了我们的线索
that Amanda drank all of our clues.
杰森就在那儿  好吗
Jason's right there, okay?
我怎么知道饮水机是
How was I supposed to know that the water cooler was...
不
Oh, no.
那可不妙  搞什么
Well, that's not good. What the fuck?
我的酒  我的酒
My flask. My flask.
你一直带着这个吗
You've had that the whole time?
我的天呐
Oh, my God.
快点啊  没错  太好了
Come on! Yes. Yes.
你想被烧死吗  快走啊
Do you want to burn to death? Let's go!
什么鬼
What the hell?
老天爷  这也太仿真了
Oh, Jesus. Talk about immersive.
仿真  你到底什么毛病  那是真的
Immersive? What the hell is wrong with you? That was real!
-他们就是在整我们  -开什么玩笑  老兄
- They're just messing with us. - Are you kidding me, dude?
我进了管道之后才喷的火
Look, it went off right as I cleared it.
好吧  我一定是触发了它
Okay, I must have triggered it.
游戏大师就希望我们觉得自己侥幸逃脱
The Games Master wants us to think we barely made it.
我肯定不是唯一一个
I can't be the only one.
一万美元呢  我不会输的
Hey. It's ten grand and I don't lose.
我退出  行了吧
Well, I'm out, okay?
有人吗  可以了  我不玩了
Hi. Okay, I'm done.
我要退出  现在就让我离开这里
I want out. You let me out of here now!
你觉得他们现在在监视我们吗
You think they're watching us right now?
-得了吧  -西三锁厂
- Come on. - "Sai-San lock and co."
好吧  我们又得找钥匙
All right, so we need another key.
把你手机给我  我要报警
Give me your phone. I'm calling the cops.
好好想想行不行
Think about it for a second, okay?
目前为止我们受什么伤了吗
What has actually happened to us so far?
没有  你怎么跟警察说
Nothing. What will you tell the cops?
不知道  或许就说他们把我们
I don't know, maybe that they locked us
锁在巨大的烤箱里  还想用我们做烧烤
in a giant oven and tried to cook us.
这种游戏里用明火正常吗
Is open flame a common occurrence in these things?
怎么可能  肯定不正常
Not really. Not really.
快把手机给我
Give me your goddamn phone.
你真有手机啊  你怎么带进来的
You do have a phone. How did you get a phone in here?
我偷带进来的
I snuck it in.
-没信号  -简直了
- There's no signal. - Typical.
是啊  我们在个巨大的混凝土建筑里
Well, yeah. We're in a giant concrete building.
大伙  我们能想出来的  看看这地方
Guys, we can figure this out. I mean, look at this place.
唯一缺的就是热可可
I mean, the only thing missing is the hot chocolate.
好吧  你觉得这游戏要持续多久
All right, how long do you think this game is going to last?
我不知道  我只玩过一次五个房间的
I mean, I don't know. I did one that had, like, five rooms once.
五个
Five?
五个房间  好吧
Five rooms? Okay.
好吧  意思是咱们还要再来四次刚刚那样的
Okay. So, that means we just need to do that four more times.
开玩笑啦  得了吧  我们可以的
I'm kidding. Come on, guys, we can do this.
刚才那是目前最难的一个房间  对吧
That was the hardest room by far, right?
往往是先难后易  对吧  丹尼
They front-loaded it, right, Danny?
没错  我觉得他们也没钱
Yeah. I mean, I'm sure they can't afford
把每间房都烧了
to light every room on fire.
没错  看看这儿
Exactly. Look at it.
这儿就是个火药桶
This place is a goddamn tinder box.
嘿  第二把锁了  大伙们
Hey. Hey, second lock, guys.
看起来我们需要一个七个字母的词
It looks like we need a seven-letter word.
我们散开来  看看能找到什么
Let's spread out and see what we can find.
好吧
Okay.
你们会留名青史
"You'll go down in history."
这个怎么样  有什么含义吗
What about this? Could that mean something?
你们会留名青史
"You'll go down in history."
你们会留名青史  你们会留名青史
You'll go down in history. You'll go down in history.
或许是哪个总统的名字  总统的姓
Maybe a president's name? Maybe a president's last name.
哪个总统的姓是七个字母的
What presidents have a seven-letter last name?
麦迪逊  杰克逊  林肯  约翰逊  哈丁
Madison,  Jackson,  Lincoln,  Johnson,  Harding.
-说慢点  雨人  -你这样很冒犯人
- Whoa. Slow down there, Rain Man. - That's offensive.
第一个是谁  麦迪逊
What was the first one? Madison.
M-A-D-I
M-A-D-I.
S-O-N
S-O-N.
不行  不是这个  还有谁来着
No, that didn't work. What was another one?
-约翰逊  -约翰逊  好的  约翰逊
- Johnson. - Johnson. Okay, Johnson.
J-O-H-N-S-O-N
J-O-H-N-S-O-N.
不对  还有吗
No, what else?
嗯  杰克逊  J-A-C-K-S-O-N  下一个
Yeah, Jackson. J-A-C-K-S-O-N. What's the next name?
-试试看林肯  林肯  -林肯
- Try Lincoln. Lincoln. - Lincoln?
L-I-N-C-O-L-N
L-I-N-C-O-L-N.
这儿有字母  但是有九个
There are letters here, but there are nine.
不行  这个也不对
No, that doesn't work either.
∮驯鹿是多么爱他∮
∮ How the reindeer Loved him ∮
∮当他们欢呼雀跃时∮
∮ As they shouted out With glee ∮
∮红鼻子的驯鹿鲁道夫∮
∮ Rudolph The red-nosed reindeer ∮
∮你会留名青史∮
∮ You'll go down in history ∮
猛冲者  跳舞家  跳跃  雌狐
Dasher,  Dancer,  Prancer,  Vixen.
彗星  丘比特  雷  闪电
Comet,  Cupid,  Donner,  Blitzen.
-你们会留名青史  -他在说什么
- You'll go down in history. - What is he talking about?
-是鲁道夫  -他刚是说鲁道夫
- It's "Rudolph". - Did he say "Rudolph"?
-嗯  试试鲁道夫  -好吧  那就鲁道夫
- Yeah, try "Rudolph." - All right, "Rudolph" it is.
猜中了
Bingo!
看啊  他也帮上忙了
Look at that. Hey, he helps.
好了
All right.
看到没  现在往后会顺利的
Hey, see? It's going to be fine from now on.
没什么吓人的破玩意儿了
No more scary shit.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
嗯  还好
Yeah, fine.
看看这  从热到冷
Look at this, going from hot to cold.
这样会生病的
You know, that's how you get sick.
虽然这问题挺蠢  但我们就只是走出屋子了
Dumb question. Are we outside...
还是去了极寒之地
or am I stone-cold tripping?
我不知道  这里真冷
I don't know, man. This place is really cold.
零下一度  还在降
It's 30 degrees and dropping.
真有趣的游戏  是吧
Real fun game, huh?
回音
Echo!
这地方真的扯蛋
This whole place is bullshit.
我们越早想出办法
The sooner we figure this out,
就能越早逃出生天
the sooner we get the hell of out here.
这儿真漂亮  天啊
This is beautiful. Oh, man,
我能在这儿待很久
I could hang out in here for a while.
这就像溜冰
It's like ice skating.
-去开阔的大自然吧  丹尼 -小心点
- Into the great wide open, Danny! - Be careful.
继续走  老兄  去看看
Keep going, man. Check it out.
-你去哪儿啊  -让他自己琢磨吧
- Yeah, where are you going? - Let him figure it out.
大伙们  听着 谁都别动
Guys? Hey, nobody move.
得了吧  放松  没事的  看到没
Come on, guys. Relax, okay? It's fine. Look.
快住手
Hey, don't do that.
就是音效而已
It's just a sound effect.
冰层不会裂的
The ice isn't cracking.
他们看着就是为了保证
They are watching to make sure
我们不会出事
nothing bad happens to us.
你们能想象如果
I mean, can you imagine the lawsuits
真的有人出事了  官司要闹多大吗
if one of us actually got hurt?
学着享受生活吧  天呐
Learn to have some fun in your life. Jeez.
做出这个的简直是艺术家
Whoever did this is an artist.
那是什么
What is that?
丹尼  快回来  到这儿来  快点  丹尼
Danny, come on back. Get over here. Hurry up, Danny.
妈的
Shit.
这些气孔
There's freezing air
都在往外喷冷气
coming through those vents.
快点  丹尼
Come on, Danny!
丹尼  快回来
Danny, get back here.
好啦  我来了  我来了
Okay. I'm coming. I'm coming.
-那真的很冷  -聚在一起用体温取暖
- Shit, that is cold. - Get together for body heat.
-冻死人了  -靠紧点
- Oh, the air is freezing. - Stay close.
-这太棒了  -他们为什么要这样
- This is awesome. - Why are they doing this?
-快点  再靠近点  -天呐  好冷
- Come on, get closer. - Oh, my God, that's cold.
我们得去找线索
We should look for clues.
有人吗
Hello?
开门  开门  开门
Open, open, open.
-你要看看吗  -嗯
- Yeah, do you want to look? - Yeah.
真正的北方是个谎言
"True north is a lie."
你在看什么
What are you looking at?
好孩子
Good boy.
我找到一扇门  需要一把小钥匙
Hey, I found a door. We need a small key.
那是哪儿来的
Where did that come from?
六个人  一件外套
One coat for six people?
你知道他们的意图  对吧
You know what they're trying to do, right?
他们想让我们为了这些有限资源打起来  天呐
They want us to fight over limited resources. Jesus Christ.
在吗  混蛋们
Hey. Hey, assholes.
这次没用  听见没
It's not going to work this time, okay?
我们会共享
We're going to share it.
佐伊  你先穿
Zoey, you go first.
谢谢
Thank you.
-妈的  真冷  -本
- Shit, that's cold. - Ben.
妈的  好冷
Shit! Oh, that's cold.
假警报  大家
Hey, false alarm, everybody.
这么大的捕鱼洞  你怎么没看见
A giant fishing hole. How did you miss that?
我们要怎么处理这个
What are we supposed to do with this?
可能底部有线索
There could be a clue at the bottom.
是吗  那你怎么不跳下去看看
Oh, really? Why don't you go dive in and check?
行吧  感觉就像在和
Okay, it just feels like I'm playing
全世界最刻薄的人玩最有趣的游戏
the world's funnest game with the world's meanest people.
我都感觉不到我的腿了
I can't feel my goddamn leg.
-大伙们  -迈克
- Hey, guys. - Mike?
快看
Ha!
看到没  我拿到了
Look, I've got it.
我是说  我找到了点东西
I mean, I've got something.
我刚爬树了
I just climbed a tree for, like,
大概是这辈子他妈第一次
the first time in my goddamn life.
丹尼  告诉我这东西有用
Danny, tell me this is something we can use.
没错  有用  那是个线索
Yeah, totally. It's a clue.
终于  有我擅长的了
Finally, something I'm good at.
你是说你能站在洞边上拿着根棍子吗
You mean you can stand over a hole and hold a stick?
那可真是谢天谢地你在这儿
Wow, thank God you're here.
我能理解你现在很冷
I understand you're cold right now,
但是如果你对我说什么不敬的话
but if you say something disrespectful to me
就像刚才那样  我就会
like that again... I'm going to give you
补上你爸妈很多年前欠的一顿打
the slap your parents should have years ago.
-真的吗  -说的太好了
- Oh, really? - That's amazing.
乐于效劳
With pleasure.
那么  现在我们要做什么
So, what are we supposed to do now,
就站在这儿等着钓到线索吗
just stand here and wait to catch a clue?
可能会很深
Well, it's probably really deep.
嗯  我都降下去20英尺了
Yeah, I'm about 20 feet down already.
我什么都看不见
I can't even see.
这是浪费时间
This is a waste of time.
你觉得这是浪费时间
You think this is a waste of time?
是啊  真他妈冷
Yeah. It's so goddamn cold.
我真这么想  我觉得这是转移我们注意力
I do. I think it's a distraction.
我觉得这整件事都是浪费时间
I think this whole thing is a waste of time.
我爬到那棵树的树顶
I climbed up to the top of that tree.
在上面发现一根鱼竿
I found a fishing rod up there.
真正的北方
True north.
什么
What?
你想告诉我什么
What are you trying to tell me?
真正的北方是个谎言
True north is a lie.
他们可能正看着我们  笑掉大牙
They're probably watching us, laughing their asses off,
笑我们像群傻子一样围着洞站着
as we stand around a hole like a bunch of morons.
-我们可能需要耐心一点  -去他妈的
- We probably just have to wait. - Oh, screw that, man.
给我  迈克  迈克  鱼竿给我
Give me this, Mike. Mike, give me the pole!
冷静下来  兄弟
Why don't you chill out, man?
你都不知道你在干嘛
You don't know what you're doing, man.
你都没把锁扣解开
You don't even have the release open.
别发火啊
Don't let it out.
你得把这个丢到底部
You've got to drop it to the bottom.
妈的  好深
Shit, that's deep.
去妈的  给你  拿好了
Screw this. Here, take this.
那个还我
Give me that back.
我很抱歉  好吗
I'm sorry, all right?
我恨死这寒冷  让我发狂
I hate the cold and it makes me go crazy.
我以后每年都要去夏威夷过冬
I have to spend every winter in Kauai.
我也是  等我不在法国南部时
Me, too. When I'm not in the South of France.
佐伊穿着外套跑哪儿去了
Hey, where's Zoey with that jacket?
我需要那件外套
I need that jacket.
太好了
Yes.
你能别在我周围抽烟了吗
Hey, you mind not smoking that around me?
把线拉上来  我找到点东西
Pull up the line. I found something.
-把线拉上来  -什么
- Pull up the line. - What?
大伙  我找到个东西
Everyone, I found something.
你找到什么
What do you got there?
又一个线索  令人印象深刻啊  佐伊
Another clue? Impressive, Zoey.
-那是什么  -好了
- What is it? - Okay.
-磁铁  当然了  -好了好了
- A magnet, of course. - Okay, okay.
好的好的 试试这个
Okay, try it. Try it now.
往后站
All right, all right. Stand back.
它下去了
There she goes.
佐伊  该换人了
Zoey, your turn is up.
哦好  抱歉
Right. Sorry.
好了  它到底了
Oh, shit. Okay. I'm on the bottom.
我钓到了什么
No, I'm hooked.
这底下有东西
All right, I've got something.
有什么东西在水底
I've got something here.
肯定是
Yeah, I'm definitely hooked.
-有了  -天哪  好沉
- Nice. - God, that's heavy.
好了好了  上来了  我抓到了
Okay. Okay, I've got it. I've got it.
抓紧了吗
You've got it?
这里面好像有个钥匙
We've got a key or something.
好嘞  把它放在这
You've got it. Okay.
这肯定是那扇门的钥匙
That's got to be the key to the door.
-谁想出来的这破玩意儿  -一 二 三
Who thinks of this shit? One, two, three.
再来一次  一  二  三
Okay. One, two, three.
我去  它太硬了
Okay. Shit, that is solid.
-嘿  本  打火机借我们用下  -对  好主意
- Hey, Ben. We need your lighter. - Oh, yeah, that's a good idea.
你们能给我什么
What do I get in return?
我保证不拿你单向组合的唱片
I won't take any of your One Direction CDs.
快给我们吧  别磨叽了
Come on, just give it, man.
好  你想要打火机吗
All right, you want the lighter?
给你
Here.
自己捡吧
There you go.
-好吧  我去捡  -谢了  丹尼
- Okay, I'll get it. - Thanks, Danny.
怎么弄啊
I don't know.
它是不是被冻在正中间了
Man, that is buried right in the center, isn't it?
你忘说谢谢了
Oh, and you're welcome, by the way.
您可真是帮了大忙了
Thanks a lot.
丹尼
Danny?
什么声  怎么了  丹尼呢
What was that? What happened? Where's Danny?
说话呀  他人呢
Say something. Where is he?
他掉下去了
He just fell through.
什么叫掉下去了
What do you mean, he fell through?
他在冰下面
He's under the ice!
丹尼  丹尼  丹尼
Danny! Danny! Danny!
我下去救他
All right, I'm going in after him.
别  别  这下面水流很急
No, no. There is a current under there.
你找到他
Even if you find him,
也带不回洞口
you will not make it back to the hole.
丹尼  你在哪
Danny, where are you?
水流把他拖的远了
He's being dragged around under there.
丹尼
Danny!
丹尼  你在哪
Danny, where are you?
他哪去了  看得到吗
Danny! Where did he go? Do you see him?
看不到  丹尼
I can't see him. Danny!
安静  安静  别吵了  都闭嘴
Shush, shush, shush! Shush!
-天哪  丹尼  -他在哪
- Oh, my God. Danny. - Where is he?
丹尼  丹尼  丹尼
Danny Danny Danny
刚刚怎么了
What happened?
你说对了
You were right.
我们真的会死
This is real.
他是怎么掉下去的
How did it happen?
叫你呢
Hey!
-他怎么掉下去的  -什  什么
- How did it happen? - What?
丹尼怎么会掉下去  只有你看到了
How did Danny fall in? You're the only one who saw.
他就站在那儿  冰突然碎了  然后他就掉下去了
He was there and then it exploded and then he fell.
是你把打火机扔给他的  现在你却一点事都没有
You threw him the lighter and somehow you're perfectly fine?
我把它扔到冰那边  我就是混蛋了一下
I threw it across the ice. I was just being an asshole.
可不是嘛  你就随便一扔
Yeah, you threw it to the exact spot
就刚好扔到冰碎的地方了吗
that just happened to collapse?
你是说我害死了他吗
Are you saying that I did it?
这可是你说的  不是我说的
Yeah, hey, your words, not mine.
丹尼一直在讲那个游戏大师
Danny kept talking about a Game's Master.
是啊  他没准就在这
Yeah. Well, maybe he's already here.
游戏大师吗  我就是杂货铺里打杂的  好吗
Game's Master? I work at a grocery store, all right?
我是说
I mean, Jason's the one here
杰森  看起来像个变态杀人狂
with the whole American Psycho vibe.
迈克  你就像卡车停靠站里的混蛋
Mike, you're like the creep at the truck stop.
还有佐伊  我没别的意思
And Zoey, I'm really sorry,
可看起来好像你爸妈把你锁在地下室
but it seems like your parents locked you in a basement
不把作业都写完了不给出来
until you finished all your homework.
还有她  她呢
And her. What about her?
你们看见她那些疤了吗
I mean, where did she get all the scars?
我曾在伊拉克服役  你个混蛋
I served in Iraq, asshole.
哦  所以你还当过兵吗
Oh, so you've had military experience?
那你可能是个  呃
So, that makes you like a...
神经病战争狂
psycho Xena.
我只是说我是这里最没有嫌疑的人
I'm just saying here, I'm, like, the least suspicious one.
行了行了  别说了
Okay, you know what? Shut up!
这些都不重要  好吗
None of it matters, all right?
不管是谁干了这些  这是想冻死我们
Whoever did this to us will let us freeze to death,
不把那个钥匙弄出来我们都得死
if we don't get the key out of that ice.
得了  现在本的打火机没了
Okay. Since Ben's lighter is gone,
我们得尽量用身体的温度把它融化
we have to surround it with as much body heat as possible.
打火机没了
Ben's lighter is gone?
Denny人都死了
Danny is dead.
你知道得了低温症会怎么样吗
Do you know what happens when you get hypothermia?
怎么样
Huh?
你会晕头转向  丧失判断力
You get disoriented and confused.
我不管你有多聪明
And I don't care how smart you are
或者你看了多少书
or how many books you read,
你会分不清你在哪
you won't remember how you got here,
更不知道怎么出去
much less how to get out.
都给我过来
You guys get over here
把手放在冰上
and put your hands on this ice.
我知道很冷  但总会化的
I know it's cold, but it's melting, guys.
再坚持一会儿
Come on, just keep your hands on it.
嘿  外套给你
Hey, jacket.
让我拿一会儿  哦  可真冷
Let me take it for a minute. Oh, that's cold.
给你
Okay. Here. Jesus.
迈克你怎么样
How are you doing there, Mike?
-还行  -歇会儿吗
- Oh, you know. - Need a break?
没事儿  我还能行
Mm-mm. No, I got it.
我还好  谢谢你  我还能坚持
I'm okay. I'm okay. Thank you.
我只是不明白
I just can't figure it out.
谁会这么做
Who would do this?
有人设计好了每一个细节
Someone who thought of every detail.
迈克  你还好吗  迈克
Mike? Hey, Mike.
靠着树歇一会儿
Hey, put your back against the tree.
-没关系 我还好  -我们在这陪你
- No, I'm okay. - We're here, okay?
你会没事儿的  我们一起
Hey, we're here, we're here.
杰森呢  他要去哪
Jason? Where's he going?
他拿到钥匙了  你们跟上
He's got the key. You guys, come on.
起来  咱们走了
Get up, come on. Okay.
-那个锁在哪  -嘿  杰森
- Where is it at? - Hey, Jason.
那个锁在哪  那扇门呢
Where's it at? Where's the door?
-杰森  等下  -放开我
- Jason! - Get off me!
那扇门在哪
Where's the door?
这有扇门吗
There's a door?
开开它
Open it.
他妈的开门啊  开啊
Open the goddamn door! Open up!
嘿  你成功了  那边门开了
Hey, you did it, you opened a door.
走走走  我们走
Move. Jason! Let's go!
等下
Wait.
哦  我去
Oh, shit!
-等我  等我  -佐伊  跟上
- Wait, wait. - Zoey, come on!
本
Ben!
大家都还好吗
Hey, is everyone okay?
我感觉不到手了
I can't feel my extremities.
那是什么
What is that?
还有什么幺蛾子他想不出来吗
Sure, why not?
往好里看  至少这儿挺暖和
glass half full, at least it's warm in here.
哦我去
Oh, my God.
怎么了  这是什么动静
What's happening? What is that?
-我们在动吗  -是的  扶好了
- Are we moving?-  Yeah. Hold on.
-我们在往上走吗  -是的
- What, are we going up? - Yeah.
这楼有多少层
How many floors is this building?
15到20层吧
15 to 20 floors.
希望他们把我们弄上来不是为了风景
Well, I'm guessing they didn't shoot us up here for the view.
好吧
Okay.
我们该怎么接那个电话
How are we supposed to answer that?
喂
Hello?
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch!
吵死了  真难听
God, that's loud. And it sucks.
真棒  这回我们要在电梯上听歌听到死了
Oh, great, we're going to die to elevator music.
大伙  上面这扇门没有把手
Guys, hey, this door up here doesn't have a handle.
我觉得我们得找个门把手
I think we're looking for a doorknob.
看看这儿都有什么
Let's see what we can find.
∮ 听那城市人车穿梭如歌 ∮
∮ Listen to the music Of the traffic in the city ∮
∮ 漫步路上看那霓虹闪烁 ∮
∮ Linger on the sidewalk The neon signs are pretty ∮
∮ 你怎会迷惘 ∮
∮ How can you lose The lights are much... ∮
嘿  那台球桌上少了8号黑球
Hey, the eight ball, it's missing from the pool table.
看那个  我要去检查下球杆架
Look at that. I'm going to check these cue racks.
可能有什么我们能用的
Maybe there's something over here we can use.
嘿  迈克  等下
Hey. Mike, stop! Mike! Mike!
离这儿远点儿  抓稳了
Get away from the edge. Grab onto something.
我的天哪  迈克  回来
Oh, Jesus Christ. Mike, step back! Mike!
别站在地板上
Guys, come on. Hey, get off the floor!
迈克  快点  站过来
Mike, hurry up! Mike, get off the floor.
我去  你看到没
Shit. Did you see that?
这是怎么回事儿
What the hell's going on?
这他妈是什么  抢椅子吗
What is this, like, musical chairs?
我们现在该干什么
What do we do now?
不知道  先别死吗
I don't know, try not to die.
嘿  阿曼达  别乱动
Hey, Amanda, just think about this.
让我试试
Just let me try this.
快快快
Go, go, go.
你还好吗
Oh, shit. Are you okay?
还行  就出了点汗
Yeah, it's just wet. Oh, shit.
好了  我来了
Okay, here I go.
那个收音机是做什么的  没准它能把音乐关了
Hey, what about the radio? Maybe it'll shut the music off.
不  我觉得它就是个装饰
No, I don't think it's connected.
上面的冰箱呢
What about those coolers at the top?
我看看
Okay.
里面没准有门把手
Maybe the handle's in there.
顺便找找8号黑球
And keep your eyes peeled for that eight ball.
嗯好
Okay.
这儿的装修好诡异
Yeah, the craftsmanship in here is just terrifying.
我讨厌这儿
I hate this room so much.
朋友们  这儿有个保险箱
Guys, I've got a lock box.
我需要4位密码
It looks like I need four numbers.
试下1234  就试试
All right, try one-two-three-four. Just to see.
这是你的开机密码吧
I guess we know Mike's PIN code.
不对
Nope.
好吧  那再试试1111
All right. Try one-one-one-one.
从头开始
You know, go back to the basics.
什么  1111吗
What? One-one-one-one?
还是不对
Uh, nope. That's not it.
那是个大型滑块拼图
It's a giant sliding puzzle.
小佐  佐伊
Zo? Zoey?
小心  小心点  注意脚下  别掉下去
Careful. Careful, careful, careful.
好样的小佐
Good job, Zo.
很好  佐伊  就呆在那儿
That's good, Zoey. Just stay there.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
我在这书架上坚持不了多久
I can't hang around on this bookshelf all day.
这可不是个好主意  天哪
This was a bad idea. Oh, God.
来  一  二  三
Come on. One, two, three.
我扶你上去
Up you get.
谢了
Thanks.
我看看
Okay.
我操
Oh, shit!
救命啊  天呐  我操
Oh, my God! Oh, my God! Oh, shit.
杰森  抓紧了
Jason, hold on!
还好还好  我上来了
I'm okay. I'm okay. Oh, God. I'm okay. Oh, God.
你怎么样
Are you all right?
没事儿  别管我  你们继续
Keep going. Keep going. I'm okay.
他没事儿  谢天谢地
He's okay. It's okay, he's okay.
你可以的  加油
You've got this. You've got this.
谁能把这见鬼的音乐停了
Is there anything we can do about this shitty music?
啊啊啊啊
Oh, God!
天哪
Oh, my God.
我的天哪
Jesus Christ.
好了  我搞定了
Hey, I've got it.
什么
What?
搞定了
Got it.
好多颜色  我看到黄的
There are colors. I see yellow...
黑的  和蓝的
black, and blue.
对对对  还有两条线一个圆
Yeah, yeah, yeah, and we've got two lines and a circle.
没准儿是摩尔斯码
It's like Morse code. Maybe it's Morse code.
这些条纹和圆圈应该是指台球
Stripes and circles. They're billiard balls.
那个黄条是九号球
The yellow stripe, that's a nine.
第一位是9  下一个
Nine. Next.
这个黑圆圈肯定是8号球
The black ball, like, that's the eight ball, obviously.
第二位是8  还有两位数
Eight. Two more.
蓝条纹是10号球
Blue stripe, that's ten.
试试1  0
Try one-zero.
1  0  不对
One-zero. Goddamn it.
这什么破玩意儿
Shit. Shit!
跑跑跑  离开地板
Go, go, go. Get off the floor.
你可以的  迈克  过来
You've got it, Mike. Come on.
吓死了
Oh, my God.
抓稳了
Hold on, okay?
那架子支撑不了你们仨
That thing's not going to hold all three of you.
-迈克  爬下去  -那我去哪
- Mike, climb off. - And go where?
抓你右边那个球杆架  这边这边
Use that rack on your right. Here, here.
你们抓稳了
Guys, just hang on, okay?
不行不行  我会掉下去的
Oh, shit, I can't. I can't.
迈克  你给我听着  从那个破架子上下来
Mike, look at me. Get off the goddamn shelf
你会把所有人都害死的
before you get everybody killed.
迈克  像个男人
Mike, man up.
别吼他好吗  闭嘴
Stop yelling at him, okay? Stop.
迈克  我从这儿下来  你先别动了
Mike, I'll move. I can move, okay? Just stay there.
待在那儿  别担心
Just stay there. Don't worry about it.
别废话了
Just go, go.
佐伊  抓住我的手
Zoey. Hey, give me your hand.
来吧  小心点
Zoey, hey. Come on. Careful.
抓住我的手就行  来呀  佐伊  佐伊
Come on, give me your hand. Zoey. Zoey!
听见了吗  佐伊
Zoey. Hey, Zoey.
天哪
Oh, God!
你还好吗  佐伊
Goddamn it! Zoey!
你必须站起来  来吧
You've got to get up. Come on.
佐伊  醒醒
Zoey, wake up.
佐伊  站起来
Zoey, get off the floor.
佐伊  快醒过来
Zoey, stay with me.
你们快上去  我去带她
Hey, you guys come on, I'll go get her.
请进  越南航空109
Come in, Vietnam Air 109.
妈妈  妈妈  妈妈
Mom. Mom. Mom.
妈妈  妈妈
Mama. Mom!
佐伊  快点  醒醒
Zoey, come on, wake up.
佐伊  醒醒  佐伊
Zoey, wake up. Zoey, come on.
我们得走了  佐伊
We've got to go. Zoey, come on!
我们上下颠倒了
We're upside down.
快点  快点
Hey. Come on, come on.
快走  快走
Hey, go, go.
房间是颠倒的
The room is upside down,
所以代码也可能是颠倒的
so the code might be, too.
好  好  好
Yeah, yeah, yeah
试试0  1  8  6
Try zero-one-eight-six.
0  1  8  6
Zero-one-eight-six.
我拿到了
I've got it.
好  我们拿到了  快点
Okay, we've got it. Come on.
佐伊  你真是个天才
Zoey, you're a genius.
快点
Come on, hurry up.
快点  本  快点
Come on, Ben, hurry up. Hurry up.
快点  好
Come on. Hurry up. Okay.
快点  地板要掉下来了
Come on, the floor's going to drop.
这是第二次这个地板想害我了
That is the second time this floor has tried to kill me.
倒霉
Shit.
快点  杰森
Come on, Jason.
我成功了
I've got it.
好的
Okay.
-好  -阿曼达  小心点
Okay. Amanda, be careful.
撑住  撑住
Hang on. Hang on.
很好  你做到了
All right, you've got this.
可以可以
Yes. Yes.
-很好  -不  别往下看
All right. No, don't look down.
好的
Okay.
很好
你成功了  你成功了
You've got it. You've got it.
好的
Okay.
加油  加油
Come on. Come on.
-好  -倒霉  不
Okay. Shit. Oh, no.
好的
Okay.
台球  不
The ball! No!
别管它了
Just let it go!
-别管它了  -停下  停下
Just leave it. Hey, stop, stop!
-别管它了  -阿曼达
Just leave it. Amanda!
不
No!
该死
Oh, shit!
杰森
Jason!
-我拿到了  -电话绳  -快跳
- I got it. - The cord! - Jump!
把台球杆给我
Hey, give me the pool cue.
好主意  坚持住
Yeah, good idea. Hang on.
撑住  阿曼达  伸出手来
Hang on, Amanda. Hang on. Come on, reach out there.
-抓住这个  快点  -抓住它
Grab on to this, come on! Grab it.
我伸不了那么远
I can't get it any farther.
你能做到的
Hey, you can do it.
你能做到的  你行的  阿曼达
You can do it. You can do it, Amanda.
你可以做到的  抓住它  好吗
You can do this. Just grab it, okay?
抓住它
Grab on to it!
加油  你做得到的  它就在那
Come on, you got this. It's just right there.
阿曼达  听我说  你能行的
Amanda, listen to me. You can do it.
你做得到的  我们就在这
You can do this. We're right here.
-好吗  留下来  -不 没关系的
Okay? Stay. No. It's okay.
阿曼达  不  留下来  好吗
Amanda! No, stay, okay?
坚持住  坚持住  不
Just hold on, just hold on. No!
不
No!
不  不  不  不
No, no, no! No, no!
不  阿曼达  不  不
No, Amanda, no, no!
佐伊  来吧  快点  出来
Zoey, come on. Hey, come on. Get out!
不
No.
(伤员验伤分类)
这到底是怎么回事
What in the hell is this supposed to be?
我看不到出路  你看到什么了吗
I don't see a way out. Do you see anything?
神童  我需要你开动脑筋  到这来
Hey, wonderkid, I need your brain. Get in here.
佐伊
Zoey!
你能给她点时间吗
Will you give her a minute?
阿曼达才刚死
Amanda just died!
你们有什么不明白的
What don't you people understand?
我们没时间浪费了
We don't have minutes to waste.
阿曼达死了  我们没有
Amanda is dead. We aren't.
适者生存
Survival of the fittest.
你能不能别那么混蛋了
Will you stop being a dick?
你有什么毛病
What is your problem?
阿曼达不弱  好吗
Amanda wasn't weak, okay?
她是为了我们才牺牲了自己
She sacrificed herself for us!
好  那我们如果被杀掉
Okay, well, then let's not waste that sacrifice
就让她白白牺牲了
by getting yourself killed.
这是我的房间
This was my room.
完全一样
Exactly the same.
这是我的床
This is my bed.
我的也一样
Me, too.
是阿曼达的
It's Amanda's.
简易爆炸装置发生爆炸
IED blast.
她是唯一的幸存者
She was the only survivor.
我和我妈一起坐飞机
I was on a plane with my mom...
当背包客  正穿过越南
backpacking across Vietnam.
飞机就在丛林中坠毁了
The plane just crashed in the middle of the jungle.
他们花了一个星期才找到我
It took them a week to find me.
我记得那件事
I remember that.
你上了新闻
You were on the news.
我的大学室友和我一起乘船出海
My college roommate and I took a boat out...
不知从哪里冒出一个大浪把船掀翻了
and a wave came out of nowhere and just... flipped the boat over.
我试图抓住绳子  结果
And I tried to grab a line and, uh...
差点失去了我的拇指
almost took my thumb off.
又潮又冻  我们就紧紧抓着船体
Wet,freezing, just holding on to the hull...
只有一件外套  而我们有两个人
with only one jacket between the two of us.
内森  他开始变得好斗和迷惑
And Nathan, he started getting aggressive and confused.
他们后来在医院告诉我
It was signs of hypothermia,
那是体温过低的迹象
they told me later in the hospital.
内森  回来
Nathan, come back!
第二天  他游了出去
On the second day, he swam off.
我不知道他在那边看到了什么
I don't know what he thought he saw out there...
但是我除了大海什么都没看到
but there was nothing but ocean.
又过了一天  海岸警卫队只找到了我一人
The next day, the Coast Guard found me alone.
那你呢
What about you?
我是我朋友里第一个买车的
I was the first of my friends to get a car.
当时是寒假  我们正在度过一个
It was winter break and we were having this...
美妙的夜晚  我想开车带大家出去兜风
great night and... I wanted to take everybody out on a joy ride.
我喝得很醉
I was wasted.
我和另外11个人
Me and 11 others were
在西维吉尼亚州的一个矿井里工作
working a mine in West Virginia...
其中包括我弟弟  卡尔
including my little brother, Cal.
然后发生了塌方  职业风险
There was a cave-in. Occupational hazard.
我和卡尔紧挨在一起
Me and Cal got pinned right next to each other.
我看不见他  但我可以
I couldn't see him, but I could, uh...
我能听到他慢慢窒息的声音
I could hear him suffocating slowly.
我听着他咽最后一口气
I heard him take his last breath.
当救援人员到达时
By the time the rescue crew got there,
我是唯一活着的人
I was the only one alive.
他们知道我们的一切
They knew everything about us...
每一个该死的细节  他们知道那件外套
every goddamn detail. I mean, they knew the jacket...
我室友在船上穿的那件
that my roommate was wearing on that boat.
红鼻子驯鹿鲁道夫
"Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer," that's the...
那是我们出车祸时播放的歌
song that was playing when we crashed.
他们为我们订制了这些房间
They made these rooms for us.
他们向我们信任的人发了邮件
They addressed the boxes from people that we trust.
我侄子给我发短信说  "祝你玩得愉快"
My nephew texted me, "Have a good time."
他们窃听了他的电话  这是丹尼的
They hacked his goddamn phone. It's Danny's.
一氧化碳中毒
Carbon monoxide poisoning.
除了他  他家里所有人都死了
Everyone in his family was killed but him.
我们都没死  对吧
None of us died, right?
-我们是唯一的幸存者  -那又怎么样
We're sole survivors. So what?
我们是统计学上来说不可能的幸存者
We're a statistical improbability.
现在他们想看看谁会是
And now they want to see who will be
幸运儿中最幸运的
the luckiest among the lucky.
你有没有勇气让余无坦医生
Do you have the heart to let Dr. Wootan Yu...
帮助你成为一个更好的你
help you become a better you?
通过测试你的极限打开新世界
Open new doors by testing your limits.
不要满足于单调的生活
Don't settle for a humdrum existence.
生活到极致
Live life to the extreme.
在接下来的五分钟内下订单
Place your order in the next five minutes
就能享受免费的度假
and receive a complimentary getaway.
好吧  至少我们知道还有多少时间
Okay, well, at least we know how much time we have.
知道什么时候会死真是种巨大的安慰
Yeah, knowing exactly when I'm going to die is a huge comfort.
你们不明白吗
Do you guys not understand?
他们挑选了我们去死
They chose us to die
来测试谁是最后一个活着的人
to see who's the last person standing.
我们现在需要你在状态  和我们一起
We need you on board right now, okay? Stay with us.
我们不能只按他们的规则玩
We can't just keep playing by their rules.
我们还能做什么  他们在监视我们
What else are we supposed to do? They're watching us.
他们知道我们的一举一动
They know every move that we're making.
他们在监视我们
They're watching us.
我找到了什么
I've got something.
快点  快点
Come on, come on.
我拿着呢  给
I got it. Here, here.
好  我们有什么线索
Uh. Okay. What do we have?
一个拳头  一个手指和两个手指
A fist, one finger, and two fingers.
它可能是
It could be...
可能是0  1  2吗
It could be zero, one, two, right?
对吧  像个密码
Right? Like a code.
不  不  不  这是拼写
No, no, no. It spells...
E-K-G
E-k-g.
是的  这是手语
Yeah, it's sign language.
我表哥聋了  他们一定也知道这个
My cousin is deaf. They must have known about that, too.
这里有心电图吗
Is there an EKG machine here somewhere?
你在干什么
Hey, what are you doing?
量子芝诺效应
Quantum Zeno effect.
如果你一直连续测量  原子就不会改变
Atoms won't change if you take continuous measurements...
只要他们在观察我们
so as long as they're watching us,
我们就不能改变状态
we can't change our state.
游戏是为了让他们能赢而设计的
The game is designed so they always win.
可我们现在真的需要你的帮助
Okay, okay. We could really use your help right now.
不  我们可以找到另一条出路
No. We can find another way out.
我们甚至不知道第一条出路是什么
We don't even know the first way out.
别捣乱了  深呼吸
Just stop smashing shit and take a deep breath.
你有没有勇气让余无坦医生
Do you have the heart to let Dr. Wootan Yu
帮助你成为一个更好的你
help you become a better you?
佐伊  你得冷静一下
Hey, Zoey, you need to calm down.
三分钟后  他们就会毒死我们
In three minutes, they're going to poison us.
我们的时间不多了  你必须冷静下来
We are running out of time here. You've got to calm down.
别叫我冷静  好吗
Stop telling me to calm down, okay?
你们没听我说的
You're not listening to me!
伙计们  这是心电图机器
You guys, it's an EKG machine.
也许这是我们的出路
Maybe this is our way out.
本  把衬衫脱掉
Ben, take your shirt off.
什么  为什么要是我
What? Why me?
因为这是下一条线索  这就是是原因
Because it's the next clue, that's why.
拜托  这只是个心电图机器
Come on, it's just an EKG machine.
不  在这个鬼地方什么都不在应有的状态
No, no. Nothing is just anything in this hellhole.
正确的心率可以打开一扇门  本
The right heart rate could open a door, Ben.
我们快没时间了  快点
We're running out of time. Hurry up.
那就做吧
Just do it. Come on.
来吧  拿着  拿着  呼吸  呼吸
Come on. Hold those, hold those. Take a breath, take a breath.
你的心率太低了  你的心率太低了
Your heart rate's too low. Your heart rate's too low.
这样没用
It's not working.
必须有人来做
Somebody else has to do it.
迈克  我们需要更快的心跳
Mike, we need a higher rate.
你得继续了
You've got to go.
什么  我不是你的小白鼠  伙计
What? I'm not your guinea pig, man.
你来  你自己来
You do it. You try it.
你看  本就很好  来吧
Look. Ben is fine, man. Come on,
我下一个来  我们需要更快的心跳
I'll go next. We need a higher rate. Come on.
好  好吧  我们开始吧
All right. Okay. All right, let's do it.
佐伊  拜托  听我说两秒钟
Zoey, please, just listen to me for two seconds.
倒霉
Shit.
我们在个金属盒子里  拜托  这没用
We're in a metal box. Come on, that's not going to help.
别捣乱了  帮帮我
Just stop smashing shit and help me.
快点  快点  再快点  加油
Higher, higher, higher. Come on!
不
No.
通过测试你的极限打开新的门
Open new doors by testing your limits.
测试你的极限  测试你的极限
Testing your limits. Testing your limits.
-我们要更快的心跳  -你逗我呢
We need a higher rate. You're kidding me.
伙计  我都快吓死了
Man, I'm already freaking out here.
我的心率很高
My heart rate's sky high.
想让我做一些深蹲俯卧撑  跳千斤顶吗
Want me to do some burpees, jumping jacks?
你想让我做什么
What do you want me to do?
-我们有这些  -你疯了吗
We've got these. What are you, insane?
当海岸警卫队发现我快死于体温过低时
When the Coast Guard found me dying from hypothermia...
我的心脏都半死了  伙计
my heart was half dead, man.
他们是用这个来把带我救回来的
These are what they used to bring me back.
拜托  这是他们用的
Come on, this is what they used.
不要  不要  这不是个办法
No, no. That is not an option.
听着  这是个线索
Listen, it is a clue.
他们把它放在我的房间里
They put it in my room
因为他们知道我知道的  迈克
because they knew I would know, Mike.
你心跳已经很快了  振作起来  来吧
Your heart's already high. Man up, come on.
你开玩笑呢吧  把这些拿开
Are you kidding me? Get these away from me.
看看我  该死的  看着我
Look at me, goddamn it! Look at me!
一分钟后  他们就要毒死我们了
In one minute, they're about to poison us.
我们要窒息了  好吗
And we are going to suffocate, all right?
我们将耗尽可呼吸的空气
We're going to run out of breathable air,
就像你在矿井里一样
just like you did in that mine.
倒霉
Shit.
你想想你弟弟  卡尔
You think about your brother, Cal.
他的名字叫卡尔  对吗
Cal was his name, right?
这是你的时刻
This is your time.
迈克  你可以拯救我们
Mike, you can save us.
就是这样  你可以救我们  迈克
This is it. You could save us, Mike.
-现在  拯救我们  -好吧
Now, save us. Okay.
你来吧  快  快  快点  来吧
Do it. Do it, do it quick! Come on, do it!
杰森  你在干什么
Jason, what are you doing?
这就对了
That's it.
不要  不要
No. No.
-别这样  停下来  -放开我
Hey, don't. Stop! Get off me!
你会杀了他的
You're going to kill him!
拜托
Come on!
迈克  你做了什么
Mike? What did you do?
他停止呼吸了  迈克
He stopped breathing! Mike!
醒醒  迈克  住手  住手
Wake up! Mike. Hey, stop! Stop!
拜托
Come on!
快点  迈克
Come on, Mike!
通过测试你的极限打开新的门
Open new doors by testing your limits.
测试你的极限
Testing your limits.
高低  高低
High and low. High and low.
一  二  该死的  靠
One, two. Goddamn it. Fuck!
可恶
Oh, shit.
我不知道要怎么做这个
I don't actually know how to do this.
你到底在干什么
What the hell are you doing?
极端  也许他们指的是低端
Extremes. Maybe they mean the low end.
加油  伙计
Hey, come on. Come on, man.
加油  可恶
Come on. Shit.
迈克
Mike
(恭喜成功)
门  门开着  门开了
The door. The door is opening. It opened.
佐伊  嘿
Zoey. Hey!
佐伊
Zoey!
佐伊  快过来  这有路了
Zoey! Hey, come on. There's a way out.
这里才是出去的路
This is the way out.
你要被憋死了  快过来
You'll suffocate, come on!
你快走吧
Just go!
求你了  快走吧
Please! Just go!
操
Shit.
我们应该把她带过来的
We should have made her come with us.
我们把她留在那等死
We just left her there to die.
那是她自己的决定
She made her decision.
你他妈的有病吧
What the hell is wrong with you?
刚刚到底发生什么了
What happened back there?
我救了我们俩的命  不用谢
I saved our asses. You're welcome.
你杀了迈克
You killed Mike.
一天坐12小时才会杀了他
Sitting on his ass 12 hours a day killed him.
如果不是在那个房间里死  他也会死在下个房间
If it wasn't that room, it would've been the next.
所以这就是你能干出来的事  对吧
So that's just something you do, isn't it?
你船上的朋友
Your friend on the boat?
你想说什么  本
What are you saying, Ben? Huh?
注意你的用词
Use your words.
你们两个抢一件外套
One jacket between the two of you.
把你外套给我
Give me your jacket!
他自己游走然后死掉倒是挺省事
It's pretty convenient that he just swam off and died.
你不会想这么做的  伙计
You don't want to do this, man.
你一直活到现在根本不是靠运气
You being the sole survivor had nothing to do with luck.
承认吧
Admit it.
你杀了他  快承认你杀了你的朋友
You killed him! Admit that you killed your friend.
生存与否是个选择
Surviving is a choice!
该你选了
Make yours.
睁大眼睛好好找线索吧
Keep your eyes open and look for clues.
嘿  这是个舱门
Hey, it's a hatch.
我们应该只要打开就行了
I guess we just open it.
然后再进什么鬼地方吗
What are we letting in?
行吧  开就开
Fine, I'll do it.
-它太重了  -得了吧 用点力
- It's heavy. - Come on, try harder.
混蛋  我又不是每天都去健身
Asshole, I don't go to the gym every day.
没用的东西
Goddamn it.
加把劲  加把劲
Come on, come on.
我手上都是什么玩意儿
What's this shit on my hands?
我不太舒服
I don't feel so good.
喂  喂
Hey, hey.
他们在把手上涂了什么东西
They put something on the handle.
嘿  你化了  你在融化
Hey, you're melting. You're melting.
-你说啥  -你在融化
- What? - You're melting.
什么  等下  看这个上面写着什么
What? Wait. Look, look. It says something.
离开之前再看看
"Feel free to leave, but may we note...
最好找到解药再走
it's best to find the antidote."
我们这个样子要怎么找啊
How the hell are we supposed to do that?
站起来好好找找啊  没用的东西
Get up and look, goddamn it!
找个屁  反正都得死在这
Who cares, man? We're going to die here anyway.
我不会死的  我不想死
I'm not going to die. I'm not going to die.
好吧
Okay.
在哪  解药在哪呢
Where is it? Come on. Come on. Where is it?
狗日的解药到底他妈在哪里
Where is this bastard? Where is it?
(解药 一剂 注射型)
本  本
Ben. Ben.
-我找到了解  -把它给我
- I have the anti... - Give me that!
这是我的
It's mine!
操
Shit.
操他妈的
Oh, shit.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
行了  这有十个数字  四个空
Okay, I've got ten numbers, four spots.
我需要一个四位的密码
I need a four-digit code.
进入五号房间  正在待命
Entering room five. Stand by.
准备行动
Standing by.
发现两具尸体  完毕
We have two bodies. Over.
收到
Copy.
20分钟以内清理尸体  完毕
20 minutes for disposal and cleanup. Over.
收到  出去
Copy. Out.
看那个  氧气面罩
Look at that, the oxygen mask.
她打算用那个干什么啊
What the hell was she going to do with that?
当然是呼吸了  混蛋
Breathe, bitch!
操
Shit.
你竟然是匹黑马
Now, you were a dark horse.
我还赌是杰森来着
My money was on Jason.
但是  看吧  这就是这个游戏如此吸引人的原因
But, see, that's why these games are so fascinating.
不知如何  在经历了
Somehow, after being burnt,
烧伤  冻伤  毒伤  并且瘸着
frozen, poisoned, and crippled...
你竟然是最终成功逃到了这里的人
you still managed to escape the final room.
你有想过自己身体里有这么能量吗
Did you ever think you had that in you?
肾上腺素  那种驱动
That adrenaline, that drive?
坐下  庆祝一番
Sit down. Celebrate.
你第一次赢了些什么
You won something for once.
所以就是你这个神经病  设计了这个害人不浅的迷宫吗
So, you're the psycho that designed this murder maze, huh?
不  我是游戏大师
No, I'm the Games Master.
是拼图师设计的房间
The Puzzle Maker designs the rooms.
但你以杀人为乐  屏幕上都留着的  都不是什么好玩意
But you kill people for fun. There's nothing good left on TV?
你杀了你所有的朋友
You killed all your friends...
就因为你不想付出租车的钱
because you didn't want to pay for a goddamn cab.
要是我就不会那么心安理得  本
I wouldn't get too comfortable on that high horse, Ben.
我们知道 文明的最初
From the beginning of civilization...
人类就对于观看同类自相残杀
we've known there was something captivating...
有种别样的兴趣
about watching human beings fight for their lives.
因此我们爱看角斗士  爱看公开处刑
That's why we watch gladiator games, public executions...
爱堵在路边看车祸
rubber-necking on the freeway.
但是现在世界的进程太平缓了
But now the world's gone soft.
所有事都很安全  所有事都很小心
Everything is safe. Everything is careful.
所以我们为那些仍然渴求野性的人们
So, we created a sport for people
打造了一个舞台
who still have a thirst for savagery...
给他们提供包厢看台
and we provided them with a box seat
观赏生命终极的戏码
for life's ultimate drama.
我们的顾客都是
Our customers are some of the most powerful
在世界范围内有头有脸的人物
people in the world.
但每年他们都想要更多
But every year, they demand more.
更复杂的房间
More complicated rooms.
更有趣的对象
More interesting subjects.
更多不同的生死赌局
More ways to gamble on life and death.
去年是一批大学运动员
Last year, they had college athletes...
前年是一批学者
the year before, savants...
而今年主题是  唯一的幸存者
and this year we had lone survivors.
他们很好奇是否真的是运气在起作用
They wanted to know if luck had anything to do with it.
幸运的人可不会被一群疯子绑架折磨
Lucky people don't get kidnapped and tortured by psychopaths.
你知道吗  当你说别人是疯子的时候
You know, it's kind of hurtful
感觉还挺伤人的
when you call someone a psychopath, huh?
我也觉得挺愚蠢的
I thought it was stupid, too.
但现在
But here you are...
我们赔率最高的选手
our lowest-odds ever to win...
活到了现在
still alive.
我真的觉得不太可能
I really didn't think it was possible...
但正如我所说
but as I said...
赌你上是放长线
you were the long shot.
所以我赢了
So I won.
我是不是就能回家了
That means I get to go home, right?
本啊
Ben...
你见过肯塔基赛马会结束之后
at the end of the Kentucky Derby...
参赛的马去领奖的吗
do you think the horse gets a prize?
嘘
Shh...
嘘嘘嘘
Shh, shh...
嘿  嘿  本
Hey. Hey, Ben.
振作  嘿  本  振作一点
Come on. Hey, Ben, come on. Come on.
本
Ben.
本  快起来  振作一点  本
Ben, come on, get up. Ben, come on, get up.
不要
No!
游戏不结束你是走不了的  佐伊
You can't leave until we finish our game, Zoey.
可以  不过我们得确保
Okay, we have to make sure that...
他死了
He's dead.
好了  快走  快走
Okay. Come on. Come on.
快来  那里有一个货运电梯
Come on, there's a service elevator.
你回来找我的吗
You came back for me.
是啊  我可不想再当什么唯一的幸存者了
Yeah, well, I'm tired of being the only survivor.
佐伊  走  快走
Zoey, go, go.
-已经过了24小时  -他情况稳定了
- It's been 24 hours. - He's stable now.
你应该去休息一下
You should get some rest.
贝尔医生  请到手术室
Dr. Bell, please come to the OR.
Dr. Bell, OR, please.
戴维斯小姐
Miss Davis?
您现在方便跟我走一趟吗
Are you feeling well enough to come with me?
是啊  你说的对  我们得看看能不能从屋顶进去
Yeah, you're right, we'll have to check that for roof access.
好的  所有人  地毯式搜索
All right, everyone, 360.
戴维斯小姐
Miss Davis.
等一下  这个之前是等候室  明白吗
Wait, this was the waiting room. Okay?
然后变成了一个大烤箱  明白吗
And then it turned into a giant oven, okay?
然后有火  有火从天花板烧下来
And there was fire. The fire came down from the ceiling.
我们没有找到任何证据能够证明你说话
We haven't found any evidence of the things you've described.
那个  看那个  这个之前是通道
That. Look. This was the duct.
有一幅画挂在上面的
There was a painting that came down.
你以前出现过幻觉吗
Have you ever seen things that weren't there before?
这些不是我想象出来的  好吗
I am not imagining this, okay?
听着  本当时也在
Look, Ben was there, too.
等他醒了他会告诉你一切的
He'll tell you all this when he wakes up.
哦对了  你的朋友本·米勒
Right. Your friend, Ben Miller?
医院给我们发来消息
We got a report from the hospital.
在他的血液里
They found traces of three different
发现了三种违禁药物
illegal substances in his bloodstream.
无路可逃
"No way out."
-戴维斯小姐  -这是相同字母异序词
- Miss Davis. - It's an anagram.
余无坦医生
Dr. Wootan Yu.
如果你有心的话可以让余无坦医生帮你
Do you have the heart to let Dr. Wootan Yu help you...
无路可逃  余无坦
No way out. Wootan Yu.
-余无坦就是无路可逃  -戴维斯小姐
- "Wootan Yu" is "No way out." - Miss Davis.
无路可逃  余无坦
No way out, Wootan Yu.
这个  看啊  这个也是游戏的一部分
This. Look. That was a part of the game.
这也是游戏的一部分
This is part of the game!
我们得撤了
We've got to vacate the premises.
余无坦  余无坦
Wootan Yu. Wootan Yu.
谢谢你
Thank you.
那么  能告诉我发生了什么吗
So, are you going to tell me what's going on?
我现在是洛根广场新一任的地区销售代表
I am the new regional sales rep for all of Logan Square.
我现在正式可以见客户了  主要产品是给狗吃的素食
I'm officially client facing. It's for vegan dog food...
但你也知道  生活总该继续
but, you know, you've got to start somewhere.
我真为你感到骄傲
I'm really proud of you.
那是作业吗
Is that homework?
这是什么
What is this?
迈克·诺兰在联邦车站的卫生间
Mike Nolan died of a heart attack
突发心脏病去世
in a bathroom in Union Station.
杰森·瓦克在I-64路上从车上被甩出去了
Jason Walker was thrown from his bike on the I-64...
体内还验出了致幻剂
DMT found in his system.
丹尼·康在密歇根湖溺死
Danny Khan drowns in Lake Michigan.
阿曼达·哈珀在独自攀岩的时候
Amanda Harper, rock-climbing alone,
失手坠落死亡
because that makes sense...
也只有这样才说得通
falls and dies.
本来也应该有我俩的死亡报道的
There would have been articles for us, too.
你该放下这些糟心的东西了
You've got to let this shit go.
我不能装作什么都没发生过
I can't just pretend that they never existed.
所有收到邀请的人都死了
Everyone else who was sent those invitations died...
而发出邀请的人还横行于世
and whoever sent them is still out there.
你就不想搞清楚吗  我们能把他们揪出来
Don't you want answers? We can find them.
他们篡改了游戏想让我们输  但是我们赢了
They rigged the game so that we would lose and we won.
我们在他们自己的游戏里打败了他们
We beat them at their own game.
我没有更多的资料了  但是
I didn't have a lot to go on, but...
那个图标
the logo...
是一个不可能的构造
it's an impossible object.
是个埃舍尔楼梯  环接到自己内部
It's an Escher staircase that turns in on itself.
这是独一无二的
It's totally unique.
楼梯上的数字是遵循某种规律的
The numbers are in a pattern on the staircase.
23和22在对应的角度上做重复序列
23, 22 in a repeated sequence of right angles.
他们是坐标
They're coordinates...
一个未登记的工业大楼的坐标
for an unlisted industrial building
就在曼哈顿市中心
in the middle of Manhattan.
他们隐匿在众目睽睽之下
They're hiding in plain sight.
那我们要怎么做
What are we supposed to do with that?
-我买了两张飞机票  -飞机票
- I bought us plane tickets. - Plane tickets?
在两周后  我去定了
Two weeks, I'm going.
佐伊  这叫做幸存者的内疚
Zoey, it's called "survivor's guilt."
我的治疗师说你要想继续生活就得向前看
My therapist says that in order to live, you need to move on.
向前看可不意味着逃跑
Moving on doesn't mean running.
而且我也逃够了  你来不来
And I'm done running. Are you in?
好吧
All right.
那就去吧  干他的
Yeah, I'm in. Let's do it.
你又不是杰森·伯恩
You're not Jason Bourne, though.
-好吗  -好吧
- Okay? - Mm-hmm.
不是吧  应该在这的
Come on. It's got to be in here.
找到了  X标记点
Found it! X marks the spot.
快啊快啊  在哪呢
Come on, come on, where is it?
肯定是这个了对吧  我拿到工具了
This has to be it, right? I've got the tool!
在这  它肯定能插进这个插销
Right here. It must connect to the bolt we found.
好的
Okay.
插上试试  看能不能拧的动
Try it on the door. See if it'll turn.
你可以的
You can do it.
-有反应吗  -没用
- Anything? - It's not going!
-看你能不能转的动  -没用啊
- See if you can turn it. - It's not working!
-试下顺时针转  -顺时针吗
- Try clockwise. - Clockwise?
-对 顺时针  -好的
- Yeah, clockwise! - Okay.
-这里出来个键盘  -什么
- Something happened here. - What?
这是什么
What's this?
噢不  又来一个谜题
No, it's another riddle.
我飞翔没有翅膀  我哭泣没有眼泪
"I fly without wings, I cry without eyes."
-这什么意思  -我也不知道  让我想想
- What does that mean? - I don't know. Give me a second!
低头
Heads down!
准备接受冲击
Brace for impact!
-对了  云  试试云  -云吗
- Wait, "cloud"! Try "cloud"! - "Cloud"?
-对  云  -好的
- Yeah, "cloud." - Okay.
再去开门  快啊  快走
Try the door! Come on, let's go!
抬高  注意  撞击地面  决断高度
Pull up. Caution, terrain. Decision height.
撞击地面  撞击地面  抬高
Terrain, terrain. Pull up.
不  不  快啊
No, no! Come on! Come on!
注意  撞击地面  撞击地面
Caution, terrain. Terrain, terrain.
做点什么
Do something!
抬高  决断高度  抬高
Pull up. Decision height. Pull up.
模拟结束  需要重新开始吗
Ending sim. Do you want to reset?
不了  干得好  我们准备好开始游戏了
No. Good work. We're ready for game time.
我又因为那个锁  把手弄伤了  拉里
I hurt my goddamn hand on that bolt again, Larry.
解除模拟
Deboard the simulator.
存活率是多少
What's the probability of survival?
大约百分之四
It's approximately four percent.
好吧  如果一点机会都不留可不叫游戏
Well, it's not a game if she doesn't stand any chance.
我们截获了她的航班信息  游戏开始了
We've intercepted her flight information. It's on.
我很欣慰佐伊能克服她坐飞机的恐惧
I'm so glad Zoey got over her fear of flying.
让我们再玩一局吧
Let's play again.